<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2022-01-09T23:48:50+01:00</updated><id>https://turtletrafo.de/en/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Turtle Transformation</title><subtitle>Wir teilen mit Dir unseren Weg und begleiten Dich auf Deiner Transformation als Individuum, als Familie oder als Firma. Wir streben nach einem Miteinander zwischen Individuen, zwischen Familienmitgliedern und zwischen Arbeit und privaten Leben. Im Mittelpunkt steht hierbei ein Leben das sich in jedem Moment erfüllend und lebenswert fühlt.</subtitle><author><name>Miriam &amp; Markus Schmidberger</name></author><entry><title type="html">TurtleTrafo Work Excellence Masterclass</title><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/masterclass" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TurtleTrafo Work Excellence Masterclass" /><published>2021-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://turtletrafo.de/en/masterclass</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://turtletrafo.de/en/masterclass">&lt;p&gt;We all strive for joy at work and in our everyday life. Changes such as a new delivery date, a new strategic direction, a new manager, a new role or a newborn child can create great challenges and limit the joy. Modern managers are expected to take care of everything and that the above events do not affect their own performance and that their teams remain happy and productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a “TurtleTrafo Work Excellence Masterclass”, which gives you as a manager the opportunity to deliver high-quality results at any time without losing your joy. After finishing our program you are able to guide teams to become more self-sufficient, flexible and efficient. By doing this you will inherently create an atmosphere of well being and security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our program is like a journey. Our central principle is living and leading from the inside to the outside. You will start close to home with yourself. Getting to know the workings of your inside world. With these basics in your backpack the journey leads you through the jungle of human coworking and existing. This phase is giving you hands-on knowledge and experience in forming human groups that are (over time) able to naturally adapt to different settings. The building blocks are seemingly contradictory elements: structure and flexibility, security and freedom, individuals and community. The building blocks cover aspects as “New Work”, “Work 2.0”, “Mindfulness”, “Empathy”, “Resilience” and “Courage to fail”. The masterclass follows the vision that satisfied people are dedicated and reliable team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;Content&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The masterclass runs for 12 months and includes the following offers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;6 x individual coaching (once a month)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 x weekly seminars - online and approximately two hours per weekday (Monday - Thursday)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 x Make-the-Change - 14 days of changing your processes through daily (Monday - Thursday) individual coaching&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;optional: three days offline masterclass in Bavaria. Costs for offers, accommodation and meals amount to approximately 1500 euros.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Peer-group - bi-weekly online peer-group meetings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 webinars on selected topics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Self-study of approximately 10 hours per month&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Final interview&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;prices--dates--booking&quot;&gt;Prices &amp;amp; Dates &amp;amp; Booking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The annual price for the Masterclass is € 7,500 in the online version and € 10,000 in the offline version plus accommodation costs. You can book the masterclass as a private person. However, we recommend receiving the Masterclass as personal training from your employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;online&lt;/strong&gt; Masterclass with a maximum of 10 participants &lt;strong&gt;starts on January 1, 2023&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto: towards Genealogie site.email} Genealogie?subject=Inquiry Masterclass&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt; Inquire now via email &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;panel panel-info&quot;&gt;
   &lt;div class=&quot;panel-heading&quot;&gt;
     &lt;h3 class=&quot;panel-title&quot;&gt; Opening Masterclass &lt;/h3&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;div class=&quot;panel-body&quot;&gt;
     The &lt;b&gt;Opening Masterclass &lt;/b&gt; starts on &lt;b&gt; 15. February 2022 &lt;/b&gt; in a familial setting with a maximum of 5 participants. Participation only by personal invitation, personal recommendation or an individual application email. For private bookings we offer a 50% discount.
   &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Miriam &amp; Markus Schmidberger</name></author><category term="[&quot;Services-Einzel&quot;, &quot;Services-Firma&quot;]" /><summary type="html">We all strive for joy at work and in our everyday life. Changes such as a new delivery date, a new strategic direction, a new manager, a new role or a newborn child can create great challenges and limit the joy. Modern managers are expected to take care of everything and that the above events do not affect their own performance and that their teams remain happy and productive.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Clarity and Joy for Managers - Executive Supervision</title><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/services-firma/services-einzel/2021/10/19/ExecutiveSupervision/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Clarity and Joy for Managers - Executive Supervision" /><published>2021-10-19T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-10-19T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://turtletrafo.de/en/services-firma/services-einzel/2021/10/19/ExecutiveSupervision</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://turtletrafo.de/en/services-firma/services-einzel/2021/10/19/ExecutiveSupervision/">&lt;p&gt;Executives are leaders within an organization and usually have to handle a
complex role. Every day an executive leader has to make difficult and a lot
of decisions. Peers, direct reports, internal coaches and HR business partners
are good sparing partners but often bounded to the same business, strategy or
vision. Supervision with an external coach gives the opportunity to assure
the quality of your role and being aware about your focus topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We always consider the interplay of all topics and pursue a holistic view of the
situation. Our goal is to provide managers with clarity in all areas of life and
to support the efficient fulfillment of professional and private goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;prices--booking&quot;&gt;Prices &amp;amp; Booking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We recommend a bi-weekly or monthly individual supervision. Our starting rate
for “Executive Supervision” is 300 Euros per 60 minute session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:trafo@posteo.net?subject= Inquiry executive supervision&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt; Inquire now via email &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For special offers for your entire management team, please contact us by email
to trafo@posteo.net.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
&lt;br&gt;
## FAQ
&lt;div class=&quot;panel-group&quot; id=&quot;accordion&quot; role=&quot;tablist&quot; aria-multiselectable=&quot;true&quot;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;panel panel-default&quot;&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;panel-heading&quot; role=&quot;tab&quot; id=&quot;headingOne&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h4 class=&quot;panel-title&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a role=&quot;button&quot; data-toggle=&quot;collapse&quot; data-parent=&quot;#accordion&quot; href=&quot;#collapseOne&quot; aria-expanded=&quot;false&quot; aria-controls=&quot;collapseOne&quot;&gt;
          Treffen wir uns persönlich oder findet die Supervision online statt?
        &lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div id=&quot;collapseOne&quot; class=&quot;panel-collapse collapse in&quot; role=&quot;tabpanel&quot; aria-labelledby=&quot;headingOne&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;panel-body&quot;&gt;
        Aktuell bieten wir coaching nur online an.
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

--&gt;</content><author><name>Miriam &amp; Markus Schmidberger</name></author><category term="[&quot;Services-Firma&quot;, &quot;Services-Einzel&quot;]" /><summary type="html">Executives are leaders within an organization and usually have to handle a complex role. Every day an executive leader has to make difficult and a lot of decisions. Peers, direct reports, internal coaches and HR business partners are good sparing partners but often bounded to the same business, strategy or vision. Supervision with an external coach gives the opportunity to assure the quality of your role and being aware about your focus topics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shanti Bosshart</title><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/25/ShantiBosshart/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shanti Bosshart" /><published>2020-10-25T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-10-25T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/25/ShantiBosshart</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/25/ShantiBosshart/">&lt;p&gt;I got to know Miriam and her children on Lanzarote. From the first moment on me
their peaceful and humane interaction with one another is impressive. Miriam &amp;amp; Markus are
an inspiring couple striving for a loving and fulfilling life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Miriam &amp; Markus Schmidberger</name></author><category term="Referenzen" /><summary type="html">I got to know Miriam and her children on Lanzarote. From the first moment on me their peaceful and humane interaction with one another is impressive. Miriam &amp;amp; Markus are an inspiring couple striving for a loving and fulfilling life.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Daniela Tigges</title><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/20/DanielaTigges/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Daniela Tigges" /><published>2020-10-20T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-10-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/20/DanielaTigges</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/20/DanielaTigges/">&lt;p&gt;I find you as a family very authentic and natural - it’s anything but
licked perfect world. Working constructively with your children and as a couple is great.
I don’t know how you do it, but I hope I and a lot of people can
learn that from you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Miriam &amp; Markus Schmidberger</name></author><category term="Referenzen" /><summary type="html">I find you as a family very authentic and natural - it’s anything but licked perfect world. Working constructively with your children and as a couple is great. I don’t know how you do it, but I hope I and a lot of people can learn that from you.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Alexander Thamm</title><link href="https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/01/AlexanderThamm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alexander Thamm" /><published>2020-10-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-10-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/01/AlexanderThamm</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://turtletrafo.de/en/referenzen/2020/10/01/AlexanderThamm/">&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much again for the tip about hypnobirthing and our great conversation in general, it was very inspiring and made the birth a lot more pleasant for my wife and me in the end.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Miriam &amp; Markus Schmidberger</name></author><category term="Referenzen" /><summary type="html">Thank you very much again for the tip about hypnobirthing and our great conversation in general, it was very inspiring and made the birth a lot more pleasant for my wife and me in the end.</summary></entry></feed>